Today I hit the jackpot.  Hi guys, welcome
to my mini vlog.  Today I was very excited since morning.
I quickly took a bath and got
ready for office.  As soon as I reached the office, work was
waiting for me.  So that was
dealt with first.  Then had breakfast.  If you wore traditional
wear then it is necessary to make videos.
So you guys tell me how this suit of mine looks.
Then our makeup session started.   There were
three celebrations happening in the office today.   After getting
ready we left and I got this
lovely gift and let's
end the party here with dance and food.  Look at this
cute baby.  Meanwhile it was time to leave
and I left for home.
After this we had to go to apply mehndi
but by the time we returned we had money in our hands.